(Amy:)Now, I assume we use this same wax
Iater on...
(Amy:)...to neaten up
each other's bikini regions.
(Penny:)Yeah, my bikini region is fine.
(Amy:)Who's shocked? I'm not.
(Amy:)So, Bernadette,
how's the wedding planning going?
(Amy:)And I'm not asking
as a prospective bridesmaid.
Pick me. Pick me.
We went cake tasting yesterday.
(Bernadette:)Raj came along.
He cried and ate haIf the samples.
Oh, poor guy. He's so lonely.
We should set him up with someone.
(Raj:)You know,
I met a really cute girl at work.
(Bernadette:)She's married to a guy
in one of our drug trials.
Well, hello? She's married, heh.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, but her husband
is in serious congestive heart failure...
(Bernadette:)...and a little birdie told me
he's in the placebo group.
(Penny:)Okay, so future grief-stricken widow
is the one to beat.